Guide to the Violet Hunt papers, 1858-1962.
Hunt, Violet papers, 1858-1962.
- Series VII. Photographs
  - Corder, Rosa -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 40)
    According to the note on verso of photograph, the oil painting belongs to Rosa Corder's daughter, Mrs. Horace Allen (nee Beatrice Howell). The envelope, in which it was housed, has another note on it in Violet Hunt's handwriting.
  - Crook Hall (Durham) -- [n.d.]v (Box 19, Folder 41 & 42)
    Two photographs of Crook Hall, one with two unidentified individuals in it
    Taken by Byran Hook?
    Crook Hall was Margaret Raine Hunt's childhood home.
  - Deverell, Walter -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 43)
    Photograph of sketch of the Church of the Holy Sepulchre, Easter Day
    Originally enclosed with Evangeline Deverell, ALS to Violet Hunt, June 16, 1936.
  - Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870. -- Nov. 20, 1873 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    By John Watkins [London].
    Photograph of photograph belonging to G.P. Boyce.
  - Dilke, Charles Wentworth, Sir, 1843-1911. -- July 1875 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    By Barraud & Jerrard.
  - Durham Castle -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 46)
    By R. Hebert, Durham.
  - F., Maude -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 47)
    Postcard photograph
    With Violet Hunt's notes about Maude on the verso.
  - Farren, Ellen, 1848-1904. -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 48)
    Photograph of Miss Nellie Farren and Mr. Fred. Leslie, in "Ruy Blas"
  - Cleveland, Charles Fitzroy, Duke of -- [1930s] (Box 19, Folder 49)
    Photograph of painting by Sir Godfrey Kueller
  - Cleveland, William Fitzroy, Duke of -- [1930s] (Box 19, Folder 50)
    Photograph of painting by John Woolton
  - [Fogg-Elliot, Silvia Hunt?] -- [1880s?] (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Fogg-Elliot, Silvia Hunt -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 52)
    Silvia was Violet Hunt's sister.
  - Fogg-Elliot, Silvia Hunt -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 53)
    Photograph of Silvia and Alice Elliot
  - Fogg-Elliot, Silvia Hunt -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 54)
    Photograph of Silvia, Walton Fogg-Elliot, Venice Hunt Benson, and Alice [Elliot?] at Finchall Abbey
    Walton Fogg-Elliot is Silvia's husband.
  - Fogg-Elliot, Silvia Hunt (continued) -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 54)
    Both Silvia and Venice Hunt Benson are Violet Hunt's sisters.
  - Fogg-Elliot, Silvia Hunt -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 55)
    Photograph of Silvia, Walton Fogg-Elliot, Venice Hunt Benson, and Alice [Elliot?], Mrs. Elliot, and five others at Finchall Abbey
  - Ford, Ford Madox, 1873-1939. -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 56)
    Taken by Jane Wells at Sandgate.
  - Ford, Ford Madox, 1873-1939. -- [ca. 1912] (Box 19, Folder 57)
    Photograph of Ford, Violet Hunt, and three unidentified children at Knap Cottage, Selsey
    Three identical picture postcards, one with "2 Back" written on it.
  - Gainford Village -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 58)
    Photograph of drawing of Gainford Village
    According to Violet Hunt's note on the verso of the photograph, "Gainford Village [is] where the Raine forbear (a blacksmith) lived."
  - Grant, Francis, Sir -- [1930s] (Box 19, Folder 59)
    Photograph of an engraving of Grant's painting "The Melton Hunt"
    The engraving was done by H. Humphreys.
  - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- Mar. 25, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    Taken on the occasion of his nintieth birthday.
  - Harboard, William -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 61)
    By A. Farrington [London].
  - [Harboard, William?] -- [n.d.] [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 62 & 63)
    Both by The Biograph Studio [London].
  - Darlington, William Harry, Earl of -- [1930s] (Box 19, Folder 64)
    Photograph of painting of Harry, after the painting by Devis now (1893)
  - Howell, Charles Augustus -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 65)
    Three photographs of an etching of Howell by Mortimer L. Menpes
  - Howell, Charles Augustus (continued) -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 65)
    All three photographs are from the same negative, though two are on glossy paper and one is on matte paper.
  - Howell, Charles Augustus -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 66)
    Photograph of epitaph for Howell by Swinburne
  - Howell, Charles Augustus -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 67 & 68)
    Two photographs of Howell, Rosalind Howell, and others at Pevensey
    Rosalind Howell was Howell's daughter.
  - Howell, Charles Augustus -- 1888 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    Photograph of Howell, Rosalind Howell, and Bertha Colnaglie at Langley
  - Howell, Charles Augustus -- 1888 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    Photograph of Howell, Rosalind Howell, and others at Langley
  - Howell, Frances Catherine -- [1930s] (Box 19, Folder 71)
    Two photographs of a portrait painted in 1873 by Frederick Sandys
    Both photographs are the same.
  - Howell, Rosalind de Montmorency de Courcy -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 72)
    Photograph of a painting of Rosalind as a baby
    Rosalind Howell was Charles A. Howell's daughter.
  - Howell, Rosalind -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 1, 2, & 3)
    Three photographs
    Three different poses and settings.
  - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. (continued) -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 1, 2, & 3)
    One by Hills & Saunders, Eton.
  - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Photograph of a pencil sketch of Hunt
  - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 5)
    By Hills & Saunders, Eton.
  - Hunt, Maria -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 6)
    By G.L. Hoffman, Acton.
    Maria Hunt is Violet Hunt's aunt.
  - Hunt, William Holman, 1827-1910. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 7)
    By Elliott & Fry.
    Photograph of a photograph. With envelope.
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [1863] (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Photograph of Margaret Raine Hunt holding Violet as a baby
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 9)
    With stamp of The Art Photo Service on the verso.
  - [Hunt, Violet?] -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Photograph of [Violet?] and three other individuals working on a foundation at Churt
    With note " Churt/ [Violet?] helping Mr [Hunt?] to lay a foundation stone" written in Violet hand.
  - [Kenas?], Nell -- 1916. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Post card.
  - Knap Cottage, Selsey -- [ca. 1912]. (Box 20, Folder 12, 13, & 14)
    Three photographs, two with unidentified individual
    Two are photograph postcards, one is a larger photograph mounted on brown board. All are of the front of the cottage. One has notes written in Violet Hunt's hand on it.
  - Larner, Guss -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Leighton of Stretton, Frederic Leighton, Baron, 1830-1896. -- Feb. 6, 1872. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Original, and copy made by Violet Hunt. The original formerly belonged to G.P. Boyce. On the verso of the copy and the envelopes which housed the photographs are notes, written in Violet's hand.
    Original by the London Stereoscopic Co.
  - Millais, John Edward, Sir, 1829-1896. -- Feb. 26, 1875. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    By the London Stereoscopic Co.
    This photograph formerly belonged to G.P. Boyce.
    With envelope with notes in Violet Hunt's handwriting.
  - Millar, Marie -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Mounted on card with name written in Violet Hunt's hand.
  - Ming -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Ming is a weasel.
    Two different poses.
  - Morris, Jane Burden -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Copy of photograph belonging to Lionel Tebbs, according to Violet Hunt's note on the verso of the photograph.
    Jane Morris was the wife of William Morris.
  - Morris, Jane Burden -- Dec. 18, 1862. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Original, and copy made by Violet Hunt. The original formerly belonged to G.P. Boyce. On the verso of the copy and the envelopes which housed the photographs are notes written in Violet's hand.
    Original by Herbert Watkins [London].
  - Patmore children -- [1914] (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Missing from collection.
  - Peacock, Ann -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Ann Peacock is George Peacock's daughter.
    With envelope and two pages of notes, in Violet and Margaret Raine Hunt's hands.
  - Peacock, George -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 24)
    Photograph of portrait by Samuel Lane
    Published by The Arundel Society.
    George Peacock, Dean of Ely, was Violet Hunt's great uncle.
  - Peacock, George -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 25 & 26)
    Two poses, as a young man and as an older man.
    With notes written by Violet Hunt on the cards to which the photographs are attached.
  - Pollock, Walter Herries, 1850-1926. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 27)
    By G.R. Lavis, Eastbourne.
    With notes by Violet Hunt on both sides.
  - Poynter, Agnes, 1843-1906. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 28)
    Copy of photograph by Elliott & Fry.
    Wife of Sir Edward John Poynter.
    With notes on photograph and accompanying envelope.
  - Raine, James -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 29)
    By W.P. Glaisby, York.
    James Raine was Violet Hunt's uncle.
  - Raine, Jane -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 30)
    Postcard.
    Taken in New Zealand.
  - Read, Sir Charles Hercules -- [n.d.] & 1908 (Box 20, Folder 31 & 32)
    Two poses, as a young man and as an older man in 1908.
  - Rossetti, Daniel Gabriel, 1828-1882. -- Jan. 7, 1864 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    Three photographs of Rossetti, William Bell Scott, and John Ruskin
    By W. & D. Downey, Newcastle on Tyne.
    Original, formerly belonging to G.P. Boyce, and two copies made by Violet Hunt.
    With notes by Violet Hunt on one copy and the two envelopes which housed these photographs.
  - Rossetti, William Michael, 1829-1919. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 34)
    Copy of original belonging to G.P. Boyce.
    With notes by Violet Hunt on verso of photograph and on the envelope.
  - Ruskin, John, 1819-1900. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 35 & 36)
    Five photographs
    With Violet Hunt's note stating that these are copies of Ruskin photographs out of the family album.
    Two poses, one copy of profile shot, four of the frontal shot. While all four frontal copies are from the same negative, two are of one exposure, two of another.
  - Sand, George, 1804-1876. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 37)
    Taken by Nadarz, Paris.
  - Sartorius, Francis -- [1930's] (Box 20, Folder 38)
    Photograph of his painting "The Finish"
  - Sartorius, Francis -- [1930's] (Box 20, Folder 39)
    Photograph of his painting "The Match"
  - Sartorius, Francis -- [1930's] (Box 20, Folder 40)
    Photograph of his painting "The Start"
  - Saxe-Coburg and Gotha, Clemantina, Princess -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 41)
    With her sister Clotilda.
    Photograph of photograph by L. Angerer.
  - Scott, William Bell, 1811-1890. -- Feb. 25, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    Taken by H.S. Mendelssohn [London].
    Formerly belonged to G.P. Boyce.
  - Scott, William Bell, 1811-1890. -- [1930's] (Box 20, Folder 43)
    Two copies of photograph formerly belonging to Lionel Tebbs.
    With notes on verso of photographs and on accompanying envelopes.
  - Scott, William Bell, Mrs. -- Dec. 24, 1889 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    Taken by R. Noyes Potter [London].
    Copy of photograph belonging to G.P. Boyce.
  - Seddon, Emily -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 45)
    Copy of photograph taken by The London School.
    On verso Violet Hunt identifies the photograph as being that of Mrs. V. Jebbs.
  - Elizabeth Siddal Rossetti's house -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 46)
    Hastings
    Reproduced in Hunt's biography, The Wife of Rossetti.
  - Simon, John, Sir -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 47)
    With envelope with Violet Hunt's notes on the Simons.
  - Simon, John, Mrs. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Soskice, David -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 49)
    David Soskice was Ford Madox Ford's brother-in-law.
  - [Soskice, Juliet?] -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 50)
    Note states this is either Juliet or a Rossetti?
  - [South Lodge?] -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 51 & 52)
    Interior shots.
    South Lodge was Violet Hunt's residence in London.
  - Stillingfleet, Edward, 1635-1699. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 53)
    Photograph of a painting of Rev. Stillingfleet
  - Swebank, Ann, 1833-1861. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 54 & 55)
    Two poses. Two copies of one photograph, one copy of another.
    With notes on envelope.
  - Swinburne, Algernon Charles, 1837-1909. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 56)
    Taken by The London Stereoscopic Co.
  - Teuchy & Cannot (after Woolton) -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 57)
    Photograph of the painting "The Death"
  - Vane, Christopher, first Lord Barnard -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 58)
    Photograph of a painting of Lord Barnard by Lely
  - Vane, Elizabeth Holles, first Lady Barnard -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 59)
    Photograph of a painting of Lady Barnard by Lely
  - Vane, Mary Randyll, second Lady Barnard -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 60)
    Photograph of a painting of Lady Barnard
  - [Walker, Frederick, 1840-1875?] -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 61)
    Taken by Rowland Taylor [London].
    With clipping, envelope, and sheet with Violet Hunt's notes on it.
  - Wiesbaden (Germany) Rathaus -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Wren, Christopher, Sir, 1632-1723. -- [n.d.] (Box 20, Folder 63)
    Photograph of house
  - Hall, Radclyffe, 1886-1943. -- July 21, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Taken by Lafayette.
    With brown paper cover with "Lafayette's Photo Mezzo Tint" on front.
    With note on verso "To Violet Hunt from Marguerite RH [Radclyffe-Hall]. July 21st [19]06."
  - Hall, Radclyffe, 1886-1943. -- Mar. 11, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Printed on the cover of Der Welt Spiegel, with the question "Mann oder Frau?" beneath it. Also included: two photos of the cover picture and negatives.
- Series VIII. Printed Material
  - Boughton, George Henry, 1834-1905. -- Dec. 1884 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    [printed] "William Grobbyns. An Outdoor Sketch."
    Harper's Magazine, Christmas
    On pages 72-80, and including six illustrations from drawings by Boughton.
    With pages 82-83 cut out, presumably by Violet, as they contained two poems, "Ballade of Christmas Ghosts" and "Christmas Violets," by her friend Andrew Lang,.
    "Violet Hunt from V.H.B. [Venice Hunt Benson]" written on the cover.
  - Brown, Ford Madox, d. October 3, 1893 -- Oct. 4, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    [printed] Obituary for Ford Madox Brown
    The Daily News
  - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- May 29-31, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    [printed] Catalogue of auction of contents of Ford Madox Brown's estate
    28 pp.
    With the prices brought by many of the items written into the catalogue.
  - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- [?] 31, 1886 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Newspaper clipping ( Globe)
  - Buckley, E. C. -- [ca. 1911] (Box 21, Folder 5)
    [printed] "Captain J. Buckley, Mrs. E. C. Buckley and Sir Coleridge Kennard, Bart.: Statement of Facts."
    With "Violet Hueffer, South Lodge, Campden Hill, W" written on cover.
    The story of a woman who divorced her husband on the understanding that she would soon marry another man, who subsequently deserted her.
  - Burroughs, Dorothy and Hutchinson, Vere -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 6)
    [printed] Card
    25, Maresfield Gardens, Fitzjohns Avenue,
  - Burroughs, Dorothy and Hutchinson, Vere -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 6)
    [printed] Card (continued)
    Hampstead, N.W. 3
    With lino cut of a bird on second leaf.
  - [Constance, Maria ?] -- Oct. 7, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 7-a)
    [printed] Wedding program for [Annabel Anderson ?]
    "Miss Maria Constance/ Annabel Anderson/ Wedding" written in pencil on the front.
  - [printed] Postcard -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 7-b)
    "Sandgate Castle, 1735"
  - Hulettsculp, S. -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 7-c)
    [printed] Etching
    [The Royal Magazine] Depicts four female figures.
  - Corder, Rosa -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Caricature
    With note in Hunt's hand on verso.
    Howell material
  - Furnivall, Frederick James, 1825-1910. -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 9)
    [printed] "Robert Browning's Ancestors"
    4 pp.
  - Hueffer family -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 10)
    [printed] [genealogy]
    Provides information on four generations of Hueffers from the eighteenth century.
  - Hueffer, Francis, 1845-1889. -- Feb. 26, 1888 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Newspaper clipping about Francis Hueffer
    Berliner Boersen Zeitung
  - Hueffer, Francis, 1845-1889. -- Oct. 31, 1878 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    [printed] The Troubadours -- [book review]
    The Times
    Review of the book by Francis Hueffer.
  - Hueffer, Francis, d. January, 1889 -- Jan. 25, 1889 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    [printed] Obituary for Dr. Hueffer
    2 ll. [fragments]
  - Hunt, Violet. -- [1896, 1926-1928] (Box 21, Folder 14-a-b)
    [printed] Review clippings
    Reviews of Violet Hunt's novels, focusing on the 1926 cheap editions. Includes a newspaper photo of Alfred William Hunt in an 1896 obituary for M. Victor Ranvier and an article on Dante Gabriel Rossetti from a 1928 Times Literary Supplement. Photocopies of all included in folder [b].
  - Hunt, Violet. -- [ca. 1889 - 1929] (Box 21, Folder 15-a-b)
    [printed] Newspaper clippings
    33 ll. + fragments
    These clippings were found loose in the red volume of Folder 26. Among the clippings are:
    book review's of Violet Hunt's novels
    an article on H. G. Wells
    The Jacobite, volume II, no. 2, February 1, 1923
    Proofsheet of an article on Lloyd George -- given to Hunt by R. B. Byles, the sub-editor of the New Statesman
    article on Sydney Dobell by S. M. Ellis
    articles on the death of Countess Markievitz, Loie Fuller
    TLS article, "Geraldine and Jane" attributed to Virginia Woolf in a note written in Hunt's hand, with printed responses; and,
    many miscellaneous clippings of contemporary events, including obituaries, divorce notices and literary editorials.
    Photocopies of all included in folder [b].
  - Hunt, Violet. -- [ca. 1882 - 1890] (Box 21, Folder 16)
    [bound] Red leather covered scrapbook containing [printed] newspaper clippings.
  - Hunt, Violet. (continued) -- [ca. 1882 - 1890] (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Various newspaper clippings pasted in on random pages, presumably by Violet Hunt.
  - Noye, William, 1577-1634. -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Portrait
  - Royal Italian Opera, Covent Garden Theatre. -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 18)
    [printed] [ Otello] -- [program with ADS [libretto of a cantata on the subject of "The last sigh of the Moor"] --]
    With "Margaret Raine" written on the title page.
  - Sandford, Joseph, 1692-1774. -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Scott, William Bell, 1811-1890. -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Engraving
  - Selden, John, 1584-1654. -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Tetley, Gerard -- June 1949 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    [printed] "The Frailties of Ford Madox Ford"
    The Footnote
    On pages 9-13.
    With annotations.
  - The Transatlantic Review. -- May 1924 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    (Vol. 1, no. 5)
    Publishing works by Ford Madox Ford, Gertrude Stein, Catherine Wells, Ethel Colburn Mayne, and others.
  - Uffenbach, L. C. von, 1683-1734. -- [n.d.] (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Vane, Vaughan -- Oct. 7, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    [printed] "The Onlooker's Book: Mars and Venus in Conjunction"
    Gentlewoman
    Review of Ford Madox Ford's novel No More Parades.
  - [printed] The Art Journal Coronation Number -- June 1902 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- Apr. 29, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    [printed] "Debunking Rossetti"
    Everyman
    Article in which Hunt expands on her views, as printed in The Wife of Rossetti.
- Series IX. Drawings
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Map of some of the places where Alfred Hunt did drawings and paintings
    With "V. H. fecit" at the top.
  - Burne-Jones, Philip -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Sketches done at Tor Villa of the Hunt's other ballroom contemporaries
    Subjects included Flossie Boughton and Frederick Leighton.
    With envelope with notes by Violet Hunt.
  - Chixholm, Wallace -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Sketch of Soar Chapel
  - Dudley, Robert, fl. 1858-1893. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Sketch of Alfred William Hunt
    With fragment of a letter to Margaret Hunt from The Illustrated London News.
  - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- 1867 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Sketch of Speke Hall
    With envelope with note by Violet Hunt.
  - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Sketch of woods
    On verso of ticket to view the Royal Coronation Picture, painted by George Hayter. A. of Alfred William Hunt on verso.
    Wallis collection.
  - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Sketch of Deanery at Ely
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Sketch of faces
    On verso of sheet is a handwritten copy of an Andrew Marvell poem.
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Sketches, mostly of individual figures
    Subjects include Lady Keane and Lady Piget, and quite possibly George Boughton, but the majority are unidentified.
    Found loose in a burlap drawing book with "Violet" written on the front.
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Watercolor of two women
    With sketches on verso.
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. (continued) -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Watercolor of woman weaving
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Gray portfolio
    With sketches (and one watercolor) and comments by Violet Hunt, and possibly others.
    With note by Violet Hunt on the cover of the portfolio.
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Burlap drawing book with "Violet" written on front
    With sketches of Rosamond Fogg-Elliot Wilkinson, D. S. MacColl, and other unidentified subjects.
    With Tennyson poem copied onto front inside cover.
  - Peacock, Mary Jane -- [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Silhouette portrait
  - Raine, James, 1791-1858. -- 1837 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - "William Morris in a Thunderstorm" caricature by W. B. Richmond -- n.d. (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - "In the Looking Glass at Twenty" [by Violet Hunt] -- n.d. (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - 2 Hastings postcards, -- 1927, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 26)
    drawing by Timberyam
  - "Miss Herbert as Diana" [?] -- n.d. (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Photocopies of Meldon Church School of Dr. James Raine (3 copies) -- [n.d.] (Box 26, Folder 28)
    Unidentified mss. fragment
  - Various genealogies and chronologies compiled by Violet Hunt mss. and tss. photocopies (originals fragile, soiled, and discarded) mapcase -- [n.d.] (Box 26, Folder 29-31)
- Series X. Research Material - Research Notes
  - assorted notes on Ruskin -- 1855-1900 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - notes on Crowborough Murder -- 1924-1925 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - notes and clippings on Lady St. Helier -- 1931, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - notes on Clevelands -- Aug. 1924 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - assorted notes on Robert Browning -- Aug. 12, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    ts. n.p.